Von Tilzer / Gumm Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Music (Box 11-45)
  - Vocal Music, Printed, 1878-1940 (Box 26)
    - Sitting in the dark, 1907 John Kemble, Lester Keith (Box-folder 26/35)
    - That old Irish mother of mine, 1920, 1925 William Jerome, Harry Von Tilzer (Box-folder 26/36)
    - That's where I meet my girl, 1926 J. Vincent Healy, Dolph Singer, Harry Von Tilzer (Box-folder 26/37)
    - Wait till the sun shines, Nellie, 1905, 1932 Andrew B. Sterling, Harry Von Tilzer (Box-folder 26/38)
    - Waters of Venice (or Floating down the sleepy lagoon), 1918 Neville Fleeson, Albert Von Tilzer (Box-folder 26/39)
    - What kind of an American are you? 1917 Lew Brown, Chas. McCarron, Albert Von Tilzer (Box-folder 26/40)
    - When my baby smiles at me, [cover page only] (Box-folder 26/41)
    - When the harvest days are over, 1900, 1927 Howard Graham, Harry Von Tilzer (Box-folder 26/42)
    - Where's Dooley? 1910 A. J. Mills, Bennett Scott (Box-folder 26/43)
    - You can't get arrested for thinking [also known as Somebody knows (HVT)], 1915 Andrew B. Sterling, Harry Von Tilzer (Box-folder 26/44)
  - Lyric Sheets (Box 27-33)
    Contains manuscript and typescript lyric sheets. Mostly undated.
    - Aeroplane built for two All I has now is an empty purse Alphabet song Am I in love? And Dolly shook her golden curls by Arthur James Anna Anvil chorus blues [Oh listen to the Anvil chorus] Anybody's girl Applesauce Are you coming out tonight Mary Ann Are you married or single by Addison Burkhardt Arrah go 'long with you As long as the shamrock grows green by William Jerome, Harry Von Tilzer At the end of lover's lane Automobile blues (Box-folder 27/1)
    - Back in the old home town Back in Dixie land Bald-headed blues by Dolph Singer Balmy summer's evening The band the good old band Barn dance Be my little honey bee Beautiful but dumb Beautiful fairy tales by Vincent Bryan, Harry Von Tilzer Bedtime story Before I came back to you Before the war Better times are coming Birds sang sweetly and life seemed complete Bit of curiosity Blue skies by Dave Dreyer Boudoir gossip Brass band song Breathing heavy (Box-folder 27/2)
    - Broadway isn't Broadway until the clock strikes ten A broken heart never forgets Brown eyes Bunch of shamrocks But she won't hang out with me by Billy Jerome, Harry Von Tilzer By the dawn's early light By the sea Cadenza Can you blame me for lovin' that man Captain of the corset squad brigade Carolina mine A carpet of green 'neath a ceiling of blue Castway Cheep, cheep Chickens come home to roost Chief Hokum Circus man College capers Come back to Aaron (Box-folder 27/3)
    - Contentment Corn off the cob Could ya A cowboy honeymoon by Will Heagney, Bert Reed Cozy little flat up town, McDonald and Walker Cry baby The cuckoo clock went coo coo The cute little bird in the tree by Billy Jerome, Harry Von Tilzer Dance of the cuckoos Deceiving bluebird Detective song by Dolph Singer, Dave Dreyer Do they know what they want? by Dolph Singer, Dave Dreyer Dr. Cupid Don't bring Lulu Don't count your chickens Don't go into them lion's cage tonight mother by Dolph Singer (?) Don't leave me now Don't talk about home Down at the barnyard gate Down at the garden gate Down at the old minstrel show Down at the old swimming hole Down on old Long Island Sound by William Jerome, Harry Von Tilzer (Box-folder 27/4)
    - E-E-Ely Eagle eye Ever lovin' baby The face on the playhouse wall by Arthur Lamb Fashion queen Female sultan by Dolph Singer, Dave Dreyer French flip flop Gee but its sweet to cheat just a little The girls of the studio Girls who have traveled Give me a chance to be happy Give me the right to always love you Good old pals Goodbye Jakalie Gotta get a girl like mother... Had the devil not come to town by Ed Moran Hair of the dog that bit you The handsome man Hannah Honolulu cabaret Hap-hap-happiness (Box-folder 28/1)
    - He did, he did, he did like Kelly did He kissed her near the moving picture show Heaven's on earth Heavy lover Hello Mr. Joy, goodbye Mr. Gloom Here's Paddy from the Emerald Isle Hey beautiful Hey there fella Hi Jenny, oh Jenny Johnson Hindu song High-life made a fun Hip hip hooray for our national wedding day by Leonard Nelson, Kathryn Bartlett Hit the trail Homemade home town band [Homemade rube town band] Honeymooning by Ballard McDonald Honoloo Hoosier girl How I love you by Dolph Singer Humpty dumpty by Bill Murray, Ed Smalls Hungry lips (Box-folder 28/2)
    - I can't forget the girl I left behind I can't keep away from you I died laughing by A. B. Sterling I don't blow bubbles anymore by Billy K. Wells, Harry Von Tilzer I feel so blue by William Jerome, Harry Von Tilzer I gotta see a man about a dog by J. Vincent Healy I guess you have to wait a little longer I had a devil of a time I just made up with my darling by Dolph Singer, J. Fred Coote I just received a letter from my baby I know a pumpkin down in Kokomo I never felt so awkward in my life by John P. Harrington, Jas. W. Tate I never see Maggie alone by Harry Tilsley, Everett Lynton I put a nickel in the slot I realize now I was wrong by George A. Kershaw I tried to make a fool out of old Broadway I want a boy, I want a girl [I want a girl, I want a boy] I want a doll I want a kitchen canary for mine I want my rib [My rib] I want what I want I will teach you how to forget [I'll teach you how to forget] I wish I could play pianner I wish you'd let me know if you see Mary I wonder did I do wrong I wrote a song for you (Box-folder 28/3)
    - I'd like to baby you I'd like to be your affinity by Vincent Bryan, Harry Von Tilzer If by Billy Curtis If I should give my heart to you by Arthur J. Lamb If it had been for you If it wasn't for you If my mother could only see me now If Solomon had a million wives today by Harry D. Kerr If they ever take the sun out of Sunday If you were the girl you ought to be by Vincent Healy, Harry Von Tilzer If you'd say yes I'll never pick a rose again I'm a rolling stone by Vincent Bryan, Harry Von Tilzer I'm a woman of very few words by Billy Curtis I'm always gettin' forgot I'm for you I'm getting sleepy I'm going to steal your heart [I'm gonna steal your heart] I'm gonna to take you for a ride I'm just breaking my neck to get home I'm letting no grass grow under my feet by Eddie Clark I'm looking for the right little girl I'm so foolish over Julius by Ray Goetz I'm tellin' the birds--tellin' the bees by Dolph Singer In gay Paree In Ireland [Ireland isn't Ireland anymore] by Vincent Bryan, Harry Von Tilzer In London town In spot light land (Box-folder 28/4)
    - In sunny Seville In that little Irish home sweet home In-di-a-na Indiana moon Isle of romance It comes out in the wash It was just like Hennessy It's a cruel, cruel woild It's all wrong It's coming soft for you It's never to late to love It's the little things you do I've been disappointed that's all I've got a bone to pick with you by Billy Curtis I've got it I've won the family over, but I haven't won the girl (Box-folder 28/5)
    - Jakey with the hook and ladder Jap number Just a little dairy for Mary and me Just a little fun by Melville and Higgins Just across the river on the hill by Harry von Tilzer Just an-other broken heart Just around the corner by Lillian Morton Just as long as your good to me Just like a baby by Billy Curtis Just my luck Just pass the buck to Gene Just the same old moon is shining Just to while the hours away Just you and I Kisses (Box-folder 29/1)
    - The last one is the best one Lay down Fido, you're all wet Let's go where they've got a piano Let's see, um, um, that's right Life is sweet Lima how have you been Listen to the Anvil Chorus Little Georgie (?) Little old Broadway Lonesome me Love moon Love your ever little lovin' baby nice Lumbago Made up with my darling Magic song Make hay hay Make me a boy again just for tonight by Harry D. Kerr, Al Piantadosi The makings of the U.S.A. by Vincent Bryan, Harry Von Tilzer Mamie Mcintyre Marching home with Rosie Margie by Harry Fox, Joseph H. McKean, Raymond Walker (Box-folder 29/2)
    - Maria by Billy Curtis Me for you Mercenary mortals Milk Milo by Billy Curtis Minstrel show Mister Broadway Mr. Worry and Mr. Dreamer Model song A Mormon's life is not a happy one by Vincent Bryan and Harry Von Tilzer Mother's blues My bamboo lady My daddy's growin' old My Egyptian maid My fair Gitana by Arthur J. Lamb My heart is the harbor to hold all your love by Harry D.Kerr My palace of stone My Sunday girl by Herman Ruby and Bud Cooper My sun My sweetheart has no golden hair My thoughts are far away tonight My twilight queen by George Totten Smith My wife ain't coming back (Box-folder 29/3)
    - Napoleon 'Neath an Indian summer moon 'Neath the Japanese moon Necking time in Great Neck No one loves a fat man but his wife Nonchalant Not so good... not so bad Not so you could notice it Nothing else matters anymore Nothing like that in a town like this Now ain't that mean Of all the songs Oh for the life of a fireman Oh grandma what big eyes you got Oh those eyes On a Hoosier straw ride On a South Sea isle by Dolph Singer and Harry Von Tilzer On a street that leads down from Broadway On a Sunday go to meetin time On dear old Mother's Day On old Coney Island every night On the day that comes before Monday by William Jerome and Harry Von Tilzer On the ice On the isle of liverwurst On the old rustic bench On the Rialto On the strict Q. T. On to the isle of romance Onward Opra is too ruff O'Reilly's ball Oskaloo by Billy Curtis Our cocktail of love by Vincent Healy and Harry Von Tilzer Over the garden wall by Andrew B. Sterling (Box-folder 29/4)
    - P-a-i-n-t by Connie Ediss Pajama party Papa's following a pretty little maid Paradise lost Party of the first part Pass the buck to Gene The place where the girlies grow by Arthur J. Lamb Please keep me after school Pretty baby come and play with me Pretty soft for you Louise Put your shoulder to the wheel Quartette of sheriffs The ragtime wagon of love Robin I'll build a nest for you The rose that blooms for me Rounder of Broadway Row, row, row for lake song Run away little boy Run him up and down (Box-folder 30/1)
    - Save all your love and kisses for me Say! Can he recite by Billy K. Wells, Harry Von Tilzer The sea by Arthur Wimperis,; Walter Davidson,; Harry Von Tilzer Settle up and settle down Shakespeare jubilee She says the cutest things She's always riding around She's chasing a crown She's the sweetest little sweety in the world Sister hasn't got a chance... by Nat Vincent, Harry Von Tilzer So will I by Dolph Singer Some day, they'll come my way Some other day Song of the stormy deep by Arthur J. Lamb Spreading the news Springtime Stealing by Harry S. Burnhardt Stick around look Stick around with me dear Straight Sunbeams Sunrise on the cross by Arthur J. Lamb Surprise by Eddie P. Moran, Harry Von Tilzer Sweet stuff (Box-folder 30/2)
    - 'Tain't so awful Mabel Take a little tip from me Take a wife Take back the presents Take me to your heart again by Arthur J. Lamb That man has something That was the maiden's prayer That wonderful tune by Stanley Murphy That's contentment That's just my type That's where I love you the most by Harry D. Kerr That's where I met my girl Then who'll be sorry There isn't anyone with strings on me see What are you going to do for me? There must be lots of angel dear in you There's a picture in the attic They all had a finger in the pie They always blame me They're after us by Harry Von Tilzer, Andrew Sterling A thing or two I'd really like to see Think of it Those days are over Those musical eyes Titles To the sweetest girl I know Tom, Ted and Ann Tonight's the night Toy that was cast aside by Vincent P. Bryan Tramp in the woods (?) Tropical kiss True love goes on forever Try try again Tune up Bill, you're off the key by Andrew B. Sterling, Harry Von Tilzer Turn out the light and go to bed 'Twas a braw brecht moonlecht necht Twenty five minutes away Two little snowbirds Two little, true little, blue little eyes Two lonesome arms (Box-folder 30/3)
    - Under a pyramid Uncle Tom's cabin Venitian days A voice from the world beyond by Arthur J. Lamb, Harry Von Tilzer Votes for women by Vincent Bryan Waiting for me (?) Waiting for the tide to turn Wait'll we're married Walter James by Edward Moran Way down in Mexico by William Jerome, Harry Von Tilzer We landed on Lannigan's landing Wedding of diamonds and tears Welcome new day We've got a little home in the country What are the air waves saying by George T. Higgins What are you going to do for me? What did the wiggle bug say? by Chris Lane, Harry Von Tilzer What does little sweetie want What is to be will be, them that always has gets What price liberty What's gonna be the outcome if the income don't come in What's good enough for Washington [or Yankee rose] by Dolph Singer (Box-folder 31/1)
    - When Dolly shook her golden curls When eyes of blue meet eyes of green When I get myself all alone When I laid my Fanny to rest When I spin spaghetti with you When I was in the chorus in the Gaiety When I'm in your arms by Dolph Singer When its celery time in Kalamazoo When Miss Lulu sings of Honolulu in her darktown cabaret When my baby smiles at me When my Johnny boy goes marching by Andrew Sterling,; Harry Von Tilzer When Shakespeare was a boy When the bugle calls to arms When the cat is away by Vincent Bryan,; Harry Von Tilzer When the frost is on the pumpkin Maggie dear When the golden rod is blooming sweet Norine When the harvest moon is shining by George Kershaw When the moonlight turned to lovelight in your eyes When the music gets started When you get through with all the rest come back to me When you hear the music in the park by Eddie P. Moran,; Harry Von Tilzer When you're down that way, drop in by Andrew Sterling Where is my rainbow of love Who loves you? I do Whose little dear little girlie... by Andrew Sterling,; Harry Von Tilzer Why did Bluebeard's beard turn blue? Why did you do it to me babe Why don't you marry a star... by Arthur J. Lamb (Box-folder 31/2)
    - Wilhelmina Will the girl I left behind be true to me With a far away look in her eyes With a look..in her eyes..far far away by Billy Curtis,; Harry Von Tilzer Within the gates of our own United States Woman suffrage by Vincent Bryan Wrap it up and I'll take it home Yes Flo! The Yiddisha wedding dance You are so beautiful You brought heaven to me You can always come back to me You can do the same thing too You cannot get arrested for thinking You can't bring her back to me You can't judge a book by de cover You can't take away all your love You can't understand You don't know what you're missing (if you've never had a kiss) You Lou you You ought to see what Santa Claus brought me You say the cutest things [She does the cutest things] You taught me to remember by James Stanley Royce,; Dolph Singer You'll have to read the answer... by Bryan Vincent,; Harry Von Tilzer You're a better man than I am Mr. B'way You're a fool if you fool with a fool You're a good old car You're just a bad bad baby You're never too late to love by William Jerome,; Harry Von Tilzer You're the only girl I love You've certainly opened my eyes (Box-folder 31/3)
    - Four writing tablets containing miscellaneous untitled fragments of lyrics (Box-folder 32/1)
    - Untitled lyrics (typewritten) (Box-folder 32/2)
    - Untitled lyrics (manuscript), (4 folders) (Box-folder 32/3-5, 33/1)
  - Instrumental Music (Box 33)
    Contains manuscript full scores, piano scores, and orchestral parts. Undated material.
    - Chinese chopsticks Stanley Crawford, Piano; orchestra parts [also includes printed parts booklet, arranged by Wm. Schulz] (Box-folder 33/2)
    - The Hindoo Harry Von Tilzer, arranged by C. M. Selling, Full score (Box-folder 33/3)
    - Illinois, Full score (Box-folder 33/4)
    - Kitty Rooney (Irish medley) Arthur E. Behim, arranged for orchestra by Ernest Bial, Full score (Box-folder 33/5)
    - The mad Madrid Harry Von Tilzer, arranged by C. M. Selling, Full score (Box-folder 33/6)
    - Narcissus rag Arranged by Mornay D. Helm, Piano; orchestra parts (Box-folder 33/7)
    - Oriental intermezzo Harry Von Tilzer, arranged by Stephen O. Jones, Orchestra parts (Box-folder 33/8)
    - Silver water dance Schulz, Piano; orchestra parts (Box-folder 33/9)
    - Untitled, Full score (Box-folder 33/10)
  - Dramatic Music (Box 34-45)
    Includes manuscript and typescript full scores, piano-vocal scores, orchestral parts, choral and vocal parts, and scripts. Undated material.
    Arranged alphabetically by show.
    - The fisher maiden Scored by Ludomir Thomas, Full score [Act I, Act II, cover pages (3 folders)] (Box-folder 34/1-6)
    - The fisher maiden, Orchestral parts [by number, with instruments in score order within each number] (Box-folder 35/1-16, 36/3-12)
    - The fisher maiden, Excerpts (piano-vocal scores) (manuscript) (Box-folder 36/13)
    - The fisher maiden, Excerpt (Act II, no. 8, chorus vocal parts) [printed] (Box-folder 36/14)
    - The fisher maiden, Complete script in the hand of Arthur J. Lamb (signed); London, England, May 4, 1904 (Box-folder 37/1)
    - The fisher maiden, Excerpts from script, typewritten, with manuscript annotations (Box-folder 37/2)
    - The fisher maiden, Script fragments, alterations, drawings of props, etc. [manuscript] (Box-folder 37/3)
    - The fisher maiden, Script booklets for specific roles [typewritten] (Box-folder 37/4-5)
    - The fisher maiden, Scene design, Act II [ink on transparency] (Box-folder 37/6)
    - Hoosier girl Edward P. Moran and Harry Von Tilzer, Script (complete, typewritten) (Box-folder 38/1)
    - Hoosier girl, Music manuscripts (excerpts, 2 folders) (Box-folder 38/2-3)
    - Hoosier girl, Lyrics (excerpts, typewritten) (Box-folder 38/4)
    - Hoosier girl, Alphabetized notebook with lyrics, music, etc. (Box-folder 38/5)
    - Hoosier girl, Financial records, correspondence (Box-folder 38/6)
    - The kissing girl [also known as The girl from Bohemia or The bridesmaid] Stanislaus Stange, Harry Von Tilzer, Vincent Bryan, Full score; orchestrated by Ludomir Thomas (Box-folder 40/1)
    - The kissing girl, Piano-vocal score (individual numbers in approximate order) (Box-folder 39/1-23)
    - The kissing girl, Orchestral parts [by number, with instruments in score order within each number] (Box 41-43)
    - The kissing girl, Printed piano-vocal scores of individual numbers (2 folders) (Box-folder 40/2-3)
    - The kissing girl, Printed choral parts (Box-folder 40/4)
    - The kissing girl, Manuscript piano scores (Box-folder 40/5)
    - The kissing girl, Manuscript vocal parts (Box-folder 40/6)
    - The kissing girl, Script (complete, typewritten) (Box-folder 40/7)
    - Mad love Frances Nordstrom and Harry Von Tilzer, Scripts (complete, typewritten, 2 folders) and Music manuscripts (excerpts) (Box 44)
    - Tiddleywinks [also known as Snowdrop and the pirates] Arthur J. Lamb and Harry Von Tilzer, Script (complete, (signed) Arthur J. Lamb, May 15, 4:16 P.M.) and Script (complete, typewritten) (Box 44)
    - Tiddleywinks, Piano-vocal score (complete) and Piano-vocal score (without words, partial) (Box OV/1)
    - Tiddleywinks, Orchestral parts (by number, with instruments in score order within each number) (Box 44-45)
- Scripts (Box 46-50)
  Scripts are mostly typescript and range from full-scale musical plays to revues, skits and radio scripts; included after the scripts are miscellaneous routines, scenes, gags, and the like. Authors are listed underneath titles. Material is mostly undated.
  - Ann of Harlem Tom Barry (Box 46/1)
  - Betty, the baby, and us Junie McCree (Box 46/2)
  - Bookland, 1910 Addison Burkhardt,; Edgar Allen Woolff (Box 46/3)
  - Christine, 1924 Douglas Grant (Box 46/4)
  - Don't make me laugh (manuscript) Charlie Burns (Box 46/5)
  - Down the joy line; A river of fun banked with music Junie McCree (Box 46/6)
  - Dumb luck; A story of chance and chances W. Vaughan Dunham,; Dolph Singer (Box 46/7)
  - The elopement Junie McCree,; Edward Clark (Box 46/8)
  - The extra added attraction Junie McCree,; Edward Clark (Box 46/9)
  - Harry Conley (Box 46/10)
  - [Ensemble of] Hello New York Junie McCree (Box 46/11)
  - Helped by the enemy (skit) (Box 46/12)
  - Hogan in society Junie McCree (Box 46/13)
  - Hoodlum College (Box 46/14)
  - Hoosier girl Edward P. Moran,; Harry Von Tilzer (Box 46/15)
  - The huckster and the ham Junie McCree (Box 46/16)
  - Hugh decides (Box 46/17)
  - Imagination scene (partial) (Box 46/18)
  - Insults Dolph Singer,; Harry Von Tilzer (Box 47/1)
  - Jimmie Cooper's revue, 1924-1925 (Box 47/2)
  - The jolly baron (Box 47/3)
  - Just around the corner (Box 47/4)
  - The love of nations [Abe Reynolds' show] Ad. Singer (Box 47/5)
  - Lover's lane; An episode of adolescence Dolph Singer (Box 47/6)
  - Marie Eline Dolph Singer (Box 47/7)
  - The matinee girls Junie McCree (Box 47/8)
  - A merry whirl, 1916-1917 (Box 47/9)
  - The milky way Dolph Singer,; Harry Von Tilzer (Box 47/10)
  - Miss Emily Darrell, 1924-1925 Dolph Singer (Box 47/11)
  - Mr. and Mrs. (At home) Dolph Singer,; Theodore Lesser (Box 47/12)
  - Mrs. Johnson's husband; A farcical romance on a side street, paved with satire (Box 47/13)
  - More nonsense (2nd act only) (Box 47/14)
  - Mushrooms Dolph Singer (Box 47/15)
  - The other brother George Totten Smith (Box 47/16)
  - On the beach (Box 47/17)
  - On the ice Dolph Singer,; Harry Von Tilzer (Box 47/18)
  - Passing the time away; A lesson in watchfulness Dolph Singer (Box 48/1)
  - Performing camel (Box 48/2)
  - The rose girl Arthur J. Lamb,; Harry Von Tilzer (Box 48/3-4)
  - Sea drift; A musical romance of the south seas Hugh Stanislaus Stange,; Dolph Singer,; Harry Von Tilzer (Box 48/5)
  - Shavings (Box 48/6)
  - So this is Paris, 1930 H. C. Greene (Box 48/7)
  - Soldier's sweetheart (Box 48/8)
  - Son decides (short story) (Box 48/9)
  - The spicy island; A musical burletta in one scene Dave Lewis (Box 48/10)
  - Squirrels Dolph Singer,; Harry Von Tilzer (Box 48/11)
  - The substitute model Junie McCree (Box 48/13)
  - The system Junie McCree with; Taylor Granville (Box 48/12)
  - Tom foolery Junie McCree (Box 49/1)
  - Trailing a smuggler Junie McCree (Box 49/2)
  - The village cut-ups (Box 49/3)
  - Where there's a will (Box 49/4)
  - Window washers Dolph Singer,; Leo Donnelly (Box 49/5)
  - A Yankee Doodle girl, 1904-1905 Jack Singer, arranger (Box 49/6)
  - You asked for it (Box 49/7)
  - You know me Al (Box 49/8)
  - Untitled scripts, (2 folders) (Box 49/9-10)
  - Miscellaneous routines, gags, etc., (2 folders) (Box 49/11-12)
  - Miscellaneous gags, notes, etc., by Dolph Singer (Box 49/13)
  - Miscellaneous scenes, (2 folders) (Box 49/14-15)
  - Scenes for Harry Conley by Dolph Singer (Box 49/16)
  - Radio Scripts for the following broadcasts:
    - Amateur song writers' contest, written by Dolph Singer and Joe Laurie, Jr. (Box 50/1)
    - The cavalcade of America. The old Fall River line, 1946; presented by Du Pont; starring Brian Donlevy (Box 50/2)
    - Hits and misses; written by Dolph Singer; featuring Harry Von Tilzer (Box 50/3)
      Features "Just Around the Corner."
    - Indiana presents (Station WIRE, Indianapolis; Book III: Indiana composers; Chapter 29, Harry Von Tilzer) (Box 50/4)
    - Voice of Firestone, 1947, WNBC (Box 50/5)
- Subject Files, 1931-1954 (Box 50-52)
  Contains the files of H. Harold Gumm and primarily includes papers of black performers for whom Gumm was an agent in the 1930s and 1940s; also contains the records from a 1942 production of Cabin in the Sky and papers concerning the board of directors of the Beverly Hills Hotel.
  Arranged alphabetically by subject or performer, then by correspondence, scripts, contracts, financial papers, etc.
  - Beverly Hills Hotel
    - Correspondence (Box-folder 50/6)